<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DirectionalLayout
    xmlns:ohos="http://schemas.huawei.com/res/ohos"
    ohos:height="match_parent"
    ohos:width="match_parent"
    ohos:background_element="$graphic:bg_round"
    ohos:orientation="vertical">

    <DirectionalLayout
        ohos:height="match_content"
        ohos:width="match_parent"
        ohos:background_element="$graphic:bg_round">

        <Text
            ohos:height="match_content"
            ohos:width="match_parent"
            ohos:padding="20vp"
            ohos:text="全部1344条评论"
            ohos:text_color="#000"
            ohos:text_size="20fp"/>

        <Component
            ohos:height="1vp"
            ohos:width="match_parent"
            ohos:background_element="#AAA"/>
    </DirectionalLayout>

    <ScrollView
        ohos:height="match_parent"
        ohos:width="match_parent"
        >

        <Text
            ohos:height="match_content"
            ohos:width="match_parent"
            ohos:margin="10vp"
            ohos:text="点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论点我评论"
            ohos:text_size="20vp"
            ohos:text_weight="500"
            ohos:text_alignment="left"
            ohos:multiple_lines="true"
            ohos:bottom_padding="30vp"
            />



    </ScrollView>

    <DirectionalLayout
        ohos:height="70vp"
        ohos:width="match_parent"
        ohos:background_element="#77C7A7"
        ohos:padding="15vp">

        <Text
            ohos:id="$+id:tv_temp"
            ohos:height="match_content"
            ohos:width="match_parent"
            ohos:background_element="#fff"
            ohos:padding="10vp"
            ohos:text="点我评论"
            ohos:text_size="14fp"
            ohos:text_color="#333"/>

    </DirectionalLayout>


</DirectionalLayout>